Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
FROM DARKNESS
What the hell?
Hello?
Hello? Is anyone here?
You can't park here.
The reserve is closed.
Hello. Per! Sorry to call you
at this ungodly hour. It's Stefan here.
Listen. there's a car parked
inside the reserve.
We don't have any cars on duty. do we?
No. there's no one here.
I'm sorry.
you'll have to send someone else.
I said.
Yeah. I'm sorry. Bye.
Damn.
What the...?
Hello?
Did you leave your car back there?
Hi. it's Stefan.
Hi. it's Angelica. So. I'm by the car now.
You fell for that? Leave a message.
Take it sleazy. Bye.
What the hell are you doing?
You're just gonna dump this shit on me?
You're the one who found the damn car.
Call me.
Maria Zellberg.
Do you remember her?
Her son got lost.
Disappeared in the reserve two years ago.
I remember.
The boy who was never found.
I've called Maria about a thousand times
but her phone is off.
What if she's headed out there
to look for the body?
Could you send a patrol?
Do a quick search?
A quick search? Of five thousand hectares.
No one has reported Maria missing.
there's no reason to suspect a crime has
taken place. So. we'll wait until tomorrow.
By then it might be too late.
If you want to start a search mission
three days before Christmas. be my guest.
but I need more than your guilty conscience
to go on.
Maria?
Hello?
MISSING BOY'S MOTHER PLEADS:
KEEP SEARCHING!
BOY MISSING -
SNOWSTORM HALTS SEARCH
SIX-YEAR-OLD VANISHES -
POLICE BAFFLED
MALMVEDEN'S NATURE RESERVE
Seek.
Come here. Come.
Good boy. Hold on.
Off you go!
Wait.
Go on!
Could you open the door maybe?
What are you doing here?
-I need a dog handler.
-I don't do that anymore.
Theo's mom has disappeared.
The police won't listen.
so I've put together my own search group.
Can you join?
I think Maria may still be looking for Theo.
Her entire apartment looked
like one big map of the reserve.
I'm sorry.
-I don't do searches anymore.
-We owe her this.
There are others you can call. There's a list
at the working dog association.
Okay.
Sorry.
Stupid of me to bother you.
Where is the assembly point?
You've gotten so fat.
Come on.
Hi. you.
-Where are they going?
-They couldn't stay.
They're lending us a tent
and some radio equipment.
But we need people.
We'll have to make the best
of what we've got. Alright?
-It'll be fine.
-Okay. sorry.
Thank you for coming. Aisha.
It means a lot.
-Hi. Viktor! Long time no see.
-Hi!
-You alright?
-Yeah. I'm okay.
Can you give us the rundown?
Yeah. I think Maria Zellberg got lost
last night in the reserve.
My colleague Stefan
found her car here this morning.
Her phone is switched off
and she's not at home.
I recognize this boy.
Yeah. been loads about him
in the newspapers.
That's the boy who disappeared
when Stefan and I had a group of kids here
on a school field trip.
Viktor and Aisha joined the search.
but we had to abort the mission
because of a snowstorm.
I think Maria is still looking for the body.
Since we have a dog handler with us today.
I think you should decide
how we go about this.
Viktor?
Could you show us on the map?
Sorry. I just need to get some air.
How are you doing?
Old memories. that's all.
Take your time.
So you've got a boyfriend?
No. we're not together.
Not yet anyway.
I need the old Viktor tonight.
The one who people trust
and who takes the lead.
Is he still in there?
The direction of the wind tonight
means I can let Noah follow Maria's scent
from her car up through the reserve.
Maria has marked
several different sites in the reserve.
so this is our search area.
But she might not be in any of these places.
Something may have happened elsewhere.
You know the area best.
What are the risks?
Lots of dilapidated ruins.
old mine shafts. mine holes...
It can be slippery in some places.
There's ice and snow in shaded spots.
She could definitely have had an accident.
We'll have to check everything twice.
The sun sets as soon as 3 pm today.
And the weather can change quickly.
so watch your backs.
You don't know what you'll find out there.
Hey. it's been a while
since you did a search. hasn't it?
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
-What the hell are you doing here?
-I'm here to help.
I hope you're here for Maria's sake...
...and nothing else.
I'm keeping an eye on you.
Noah. scent... Scent.
Scent.
Scent. Good boy.
What did you find?
What did you find there. boy?
-Could you take a look at this?
-Yeah. sure.
Something's happening.
He's picked up her trail.
Good boy. Seek!
Aisha to the search group.
Doing a radio check.
Can everyone hear me? Over.
Angelica here. I hear you. Over.
I hear you too. Over.
Viktor is listening. Over.
And I hear all of you.
Good luck and be careful out there.
Over and out.
Maria!
BOOK OF BLACK MAGIC
Good boy. good boy.
Seek. Noah!
Angelica to Aisha. Over.
Listening.
Hey. I've been looking through Maria's stuff.
It's full of old texts
and pictures and sketches.
Any clues?
No. I don't think so.
But there's a weird sketch here.
I don't know what it is.
Some scary woman.
Okay. that sounds like the cave wraith.
It's an old myth that we tell
to scare the summer tourists.
Okay. thanks. Aisha. Let us know
if you find something useful.
Okay. Over and out.
So what's the story with this cave wraith?
Is this place haunted or what?
It's superstition.
They mined ore here in the 1800s.
There were a lot of accidents.
so they thought they'd dug
too deep into the ground
and released some kind of evil entity
that was guarding the ore.
She was referred to as the cave wraith.
It was said that she...
...used the darkness
to lure the miners to their deaths.
The foreman got so desperate
that he began sacrificing cattle
to mine the ore in peace.
And then. when the mine was depleted.
they banned the villagers from coming out
here during the darkest months of the year.
They were afraid that she was still out here.
We kept that rule
when the area became a reserve.
Not because of the cave wraith
but to prevent accidents.
So...
Maria believes that it's the cave wraith
who has taken her son?
She's probably leaving no stone unturned
to try to understand what happened.
I get that.
How can a child just disappear like that?
Viktor!
Did you see something?
No. nothing.
We're here.
And we're done searching this area.
And we need to avoid the marshland...
We should probably head north.
I need to take a piss.
Do you want some coffee?
Are you sure? You're cold.
Just need to get my blood circulation going.
Does it hurt?
Phantom pains.
I can't feel my hand anymore.
Can you feel this?
-Nothing.
-Nothing?
Isn't it strange how you can feel pain
in something that doesn't exist anymore?
What's this?
Did you cut yourself?
-Why didn't you tell me?
-We weren't talking.
No. because you stopped calling.
I have never judged you for what happened.
We were fighting a fucking blizzard.
Angelica.
Was there coffee?
There are plastic cups in my backpack.
The lid will do just fine.
You're not afraid of my germs. are you?
-Where are you going?
-To pee.
Want to hold hands?
Is anyone there?
Hello?
Wait... Wait!
Theo!
Is anyone there?
Viktor. where the hell are you?
Sorry. I'm on my way back.
I thought I saw something.
Angelica!
Angelica. help!
Are you okay?
What the hell are you doing?
You could have gotten yourself killed!
I thought I saw something.
Maria?
I don't know.
What the hell do you mean?
Who else would it have been?
Hey. calm down.
What did you see?
It was probably just...
Maybe it was an animal.
I thought I saw something...
and then I took a false step.
Look. I know you.
You would never mistake
a human being for an animal.
Well. I did.
You may not trust your own judgment
anymore. but I do.
What did you see?
-I thought I saw Theo.
-What?
But I can't have.
I'm probably just very tired.
Coffee.
-Drink up.
-Thanks.
Aisha to Angelica. Over.
Listening. Over.
-I was just contacted by Bengt.
-From the police?
Yes. He's been in contact
with Maria's family.
They've filed a missing person's report.
He's going to her apartment now.
but wanted to tell you
he'll be here tomorrow morning.
Wonderful!
Ward 36. How can I help you?
Sorry. who have I reached?
You have reached ward 36
of the general psychiatric clinic.
Angelica to Aisha. Over.
I just spoke to Maria's doctor.
She's been hospitalized
for self-harm and depression.
-Aisha?
-Two weeks ago. she discharged herself.
Aisha?
We can't hear you.
Skip zone.
What's he doing?
He's confused.
The trail is dividing.
One is breaking off that way. and one
goes straight ahead on the path there.
How the hell can they be splitting?
There could be someone
other than Maria out here. for example.
Oh. come on.
He's probably confused. he's tired.
Angelica and I'll follow the trail
that leads into the forest here.
Johan. you can stay on the path.
It's easier.
No. forget it.
You take the forest. With your dog.
-Angelica and I. we'll stay on the path.
-Okay.
No. no one goes alone.
He's not alone.
He's got his best friend with him.
Let's go! He can use the radio
if something happens.
Okay. Please. be careful.
Sure.
It's okay. boy.
Okay?
Can anyone hear me?
Viktor to Aisha. Over.
Can you guys hear me?
Maria?
Is that you?
Are you there?
What's the matter?
Would you have preferred
to go with him?
Please. just stop it.
I saw you. you know.
Back by the shelter.
I saw you acting all sweet.
Just 'cause we slept together a few times
doesn't mean I want to get married.
-So what does it mean?
-Are we doing this now?
-Are you in a hurry to get somewhere?
-Yes. I am!
Is this one of those girl things
that you think you're going to save him
or what the hell?
You have no idea
what we've been through.
Oh. come on!
You're practically drooling over him.
I was pregnant when we searched for Theo.
Viktor wanted to call off the search.
but I was so damn stubborn...
I thought...
I don't know what I was thinking.
I thought that...
That if we could just find Theo.
it would be worth the risk.
We didn't find anything.
And then when we got to the hospital...
...the baby was dead.
I had no idea.
What did you find?
What did you find. boy?
Seek!
What is it you've found?
Huh?
What have you found?
Yes... Yes.
Show me.
Hello?
Noah!
Hey. boy.
What have you found?
What's that? What have you found?
Yes. what've you found?
What do you see?
Hello?
Angelica. Over.
Angelica. Listening.
Noah has found something.
Someone's moving around in the forest.
But we lost the trail here at the fen.
and I think the ground is marshy.
so I honestly don't dare go over.
Do you think it was Maria?
I couldn't see. It happened too fast.
Where are you now?
At the edge of the fen.
Johan has a GPS receiver.
he should be able to see Noah.
Look out over the fen.
I can see you.
Did you see in what direction
the person disappeared?
Negative. But I can send up my drone.
Good. Let us know when it's airborne.
We'll stay here. Over and out.
I'm in the air now.
We can see the drone.
I can see you.
There's something behind you.
What?
Where?
-There's someone in the forest!
-Where?
Are you sure about that?
I don't see anything.
Stay where you are.
I'll try to get it on camera. okay?
What are you talking about?
Isn't it just some animal?
I have to get the drone lower to see better.
Viktor. what do you see?
Answer.
Viktor. answer. What do you see?
Talk to us! What do you see?
Damn it!
There was something there.
Are you sure. Viktor?
Yes. it broke the drone.
Follow the GPS. I'm heading for the drone.
Come here. Jump! Good boy!
Might have to take
some more flying lessons. huh?
-What is that?
-Nothing.
No. what is that?
Hey. what do you have there?
Show me. for fuck's sake.
For psychosis.
Does Angelica know about this?
Give me those.
You didn't see anything
with the drone. did you?
Shut up!
You just want to keep her out here.
don't you?
You're no fucking good for her. Viktor!
Don't you get that?
You make her dig up old shit
she'd be better off forgetting about.
Stay the fuck away.
Hey...
...she told me.
I know you killed two children last time.
Stop!
-What the hell are you doing?
-He's the one who attacked me!
He's completely fucking insane.
-And you're completely innocent. are you?
-He sees things that aren't there.
Stop.
He takes these.
I bet he's been chasing
his own damn delusions with the drone.
Viktor? Huh? Is this true?
Theo!
-We can't stay here any longer.
-Theo!
Angelica. there are no signs of him!
I can go on a little longer.
A little longer... A little longer. okay?
-The snowmobile is already on its way!
-Theo!
Angelica!
Aisha. where the hell is
that damn snowmobile?
-It's on its way. Viktor...
-We need it now!
-What was that?
-Just the wind.
Here!
Over here!
What you saw on the drone by
the mine shaft... Was that all in your head?
It doesn't work that way.
Okay. so how does it work?
How long have you been taking these?
Huh?
Johan must think I'm an idiot
for defending you.
What the hell should I tell Aisha?
I'm sorry.
I should have said something.
I'm deciding that we're going back now.
Aisha to Johan. Over.
Are you there?
Well. we can't hear you
but maybe you can hear us.
We are calling off the search now.
We should be back in an hour or so.
Over and out.
No. I'll take Noah.
Don't want to risk him
chasing after your delusions.
Wait! Look.
Maria has marked those ruins on her map.
I saw pictures of it in her apartment.
What if it was Maria
that you saw on the drone?
Angelica. we're calling this off now.
Might as well check while we're here.
Come on. damn it!
Viktor shouldn't be out here
for another fucking second.
We have no cell service
and we have no radio contact with Aisha
in case something happens.
We don't know what I saw.
That's the most fucking
reasonable thing you've said all night.
-Fine. you'll have to go without me.
-You get ten minutes. Okay?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Seven minutes.
What is this place anyway?
-They had their midwinter sacrifices here.
-Midwinter sacrifices?
Like a ritual sacrifice.
To the cave wraith?
Yes. it was tradition to hold a midwinter
sacrifice on the darkest day of the year.
In exchange for a blood sacrifice.
she was asked for a favor.
Like showing where the ore was located
or curing diseases.
So if I sacrifice Noah right now.
she can make sure I get home to my bed.
Funny.
Did they sacrifice people too?
Of course they didn't.
You are not real. You are not real.
How the hell do you get the dog to shut up?
Look at me. Viktor. Look at me.
Look at me. Viktor!
There is no one there!
Viktor. Viktor. Look at me!
-Fucking do something!
-What the hell am I supposed to do?
Viktor!
Breathe with me. Viktor. I'm here.
Here I am. Here I am. Viktor. Viktor...
There. there. there... Viktor. Viktor!
Breathe with me. okay? Breathe with me.
Come on. breathe with me.
In. in. in...
...and out.
In...and out.
That must be Maria's.
I knew it.
What are you doing?
Can you check the ruins with Noah.
if you're up for it?
Johan and I will take the outside.
-No. we're going back now.
-Just a little while longer.
No. that's enough!
We're going back right now.
No. just a little while longer!
Look at Viktor! He's fucking exhausted!
-So you decide for him?
-Well. I'm deciding that I'm leaving.
My sweet darling. please.
Come with me now.
Don't do this.
I'll make sure Aisha blacklists
the both of you.
Seek!
Aisha?
-Aisha!
-Angelica!
Is she alive?!
Do something! Do something!
Help her!
Do something!
Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Is she alive?
We have to get out of here.
Johan. Over.
Johan. Where are you?
Can you please answer?
What the hell is it?
Did you guys change your minds?
Johan. where are you?
We're on our way back.
I just passed the fen.
-Okay. you have to wait for us.
-Is something wrong?
We'll tell you when we see you.
Angelica. what the hell happened?
Did he do something to you?
-Can you just wait?
-Are you here already?
What are you talking about?
I can see one of you.
We can't see you.
Okay. if it's not you.
then who the hell is it?
Johan. come back to us.
Hey. who the hell are you? Show yourself.
-Get out of there!
-Johan. run!
-Stop. damn it!
-The fen.
-Johan!
-Noah. come on!
Johan!
Good boy... Look.
Good. Noah.
He can't have gotten far without these.
Hey. hey. hey...
Take Noah.
Johan!
Johan?
Johan. can you hear me?
Johan!
What's wrong with Johan?
No! No...
Johan! Johan... Johan!
-No!
-He's gone.
Johan!
-Stop! Don't...
-Angelica. he's gone.
-Stop it! Let go of me.
-He's gone.
Angelica. he's gone. He's gone.
Steady. Breathe. breathe. breathe. breathe.
-Let me go! Let me go!
-Breathe.
Calm down. It's alright. Good. come here...
Mayday. mayday! Two people in distress
in Malmveden's Nature Reserve.
Can anyone hear us?
Mayday. mayday! Can anyone hear us?
If anyone can hear us. contact the police
and emergency services immediately.
Okay...
Can you keep going?
I think I know
how we can let them know where we are.
If the police find Noah.
they'll see on the GPS receiver
where the dog tracker is.
Okay?
Do you want to ride in the car? Yes. the car.
Yes. find the car.
Yes. find the car. Find the car!
I'll make a fire. I'll go get some firewood.
I'll be close by. okay?
You can't walk off like that.
There isn't supposed be a cave here.
-No. no. no...
-What's wrong with you?
There's something there.
What do you mean?
Angelica. wait!
Angelica!
Where are you?
What the hell was that? What the hell
was it? What made that noise?
I don't know.
But whatever it was. we've lost it.
Do you know where we are?
No... Yes.
There's almost no snow here.
We must be in the valley.
I know that road.
If we go that way.
we'll get back to the tent.
-It's no more than a kilometer.
-Okay. good.
Come on.
Angelica. look.
What the hell. that's Stefan's car.
I thought he'd left.
Were there any keys?
Shit. there's blood on the seat.
Angelica...
Someone's turned on a light. We won't
go straight up. we'll go around okay?
Okay.
Stefan?
Someone's been here.
We have a car.
Back up!
I don't want to hurt you. Understand?
Just let me leave.
Maria...
Who the hell are you?
My name is Angelica.
I'm from park management.
And this is Viktor. he's a dog handler.
-How the hell do you know who I am?
-Because we've been looking for you.
We came here because we wanted
to know that you're okay.
Careful.
She's terrified.
Maria...
I'm approaching you now. okay?
I just want to make sure you're not hurt.
There.
There...
Is this yours?
Where did all the blood come from?
He attacked me.
Who?
Maria...
There's a car down by the road.
The man driving the car.
was he the one who attacked you?
-He just lunged at me.
-Stefan?
I hit him in the face with a rock.
and he stopped moving.
Then I ran away and found the cabin
and hid in here.
Why didn't you take the car?
What about the radio?
Testing one. two. One. two.
It's on our channel.
You must have heard that we were here.
Please stop. Viktor.
She's obviously in shock.
Okay. get some rest.
We'll get you out of here
as soon as we can.
Let's talk in the kitchen.
It's fucking crazy what's happening out here.
I think Maria is lying.
She didn't come here to hide from Stefan.
she came here to hide from us.
Be serious. You can see
the condition she's in. can't you?
Her radio was working.
She heard everything we said.
knew exactly where we were
and still stayed away.
Then when we stopped using the radios.
we found her right away.
-Don't you think that's strange?
-What do you want to do?
-I think we should leave her here.
-What? We found her.
We've done what we came here to do.
Let's get out of here together.
Something's not right here.
We will be home in an hour.
Here you go.
Come on.
Okay...
Sit down and get some rest
and we'll leave in a minute.
Oh God. you're still cold as ice.
-Do you have her sweater?
-It's in my backpack up at the house.
Are you coming?
Where did you get this?
I can explain...
There were traces.
but you didn't say anything.
Because I had my hands goddamn full
trying to save you.
Could we have saved Theo?
Could we have saved him?
Can you please talk to me?
Can you say...
Can you for once just talk to me?
What does it fucking matter?
-It's his own fault that he is dead.
-Well. it matters to me.
At least one child
would have been alive still.
-We don't owe him anything.
-Why did you come here today?
-Angelica...
-No.
Who are you. Viktor?
Who the hell have you become?
Viktor!
What happened?
Hey!
Stefan? What happened?
That fucking cunt...
She said she was going to kill me.
Who?
Stefan?
Who? Stefan. did Maria do this?
She said she was going to sacrifice me
at midnight...
...to get her son back.
Look at me! Look at me!
Look at me!
Damn!
Angelica. I'm on my way now.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Angelica!
Angelica?
Fuck!
Angelica. where are you?
Angelica. if you hear me.
shout as loud as you can.
-Viktor!
-Turn around.
Maria. don't do anything crazy.
Maybe we can help each other.
Tell me what you need.
I don't need your help.
But I know where Theo is.
You're lying.
No. I'm not lying.
I can bring him to you...
...but then you have to promise
not to hurt Angelica. okay?
You have until midnight.
-Viktor!
-Shut up!
-Let me go!
-Walk!
- I'm begging you. Let me go!
- Walk!
-Get on your knees.
-Stop it!
-Please. please. please.
I'll do anything... I'm begging you!
On your knees!
Stop. Stop. stop. please...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
Maria!
Angelica!
Theo...
Sweetheart.
Theo. you came back.
There you go...
Look at me. Alright?
I'm cold...
Everything's alright.
Theo?
Theo!
You can do this. okay?
-Viktor. I'm sorry...
-Angelica?
Angelica. look at me.
Look at me. Look at me.
No. no. no. no. no...
Angelica!
Angelica! Don't die. You can't die.
Theo.
Let me get her back.
You have gotten your sacrifice.
Let me have her back.
Bring her back to life.
Hey...
Viktor?
I'm here. I'm here.
You're bleeding.
Hello?
Is there anyone here?
Angelica?
Aisha?
God!
Trying to scare me to death. huh?
Where is your owner?
What do you have there?
Think you can help me?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org